export const QUESTION_CATEGORIES = {
    0: 'FOOD',
    1: 'SPORTS',
    2: 'HISTORY'
}

export const QUESTIONS = [
    [
        {
            question: 'What kind of food is usually raw fish and rice.',
            answer: 'Sushi'
        },
        {
            question: 'Bacon and eggs are most commonly eaten for which meal?',
            answer: 'Breakfast'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is a common side for an American fast food meal',
            answer: 'Fries'
        },
        {
            question: 'Name the fruit that Johnny Appleseed helped plant.',
            answer: 'Apple'
        },
        {
            question: 'Complete the sentence. Macaroni and',
            answer: 'Cheese'
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            question: 'What is the name of Seattle\'s football team',
            answer: 'Seahawks'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which sport do the Lakers play?',
            answer: 'Basketball'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which swimmer has the most Olympic gold medals in history?',
            answer: 'Michael Phelps'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which football player is nicknamed Beast Mode',
            answer: 'Marshawn Lynch'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the mascot of the University of Washington',
            answer: 'Husky'
        }        
    ],
    [
        {
            question: 'Which year was Barack Obama first elected president',
            answer: '2008'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which president is known for ping-pong diplomacy?',
            answer: 'Richard Nixon'
        },
        {
            question: 'Mahatma Gandhi was a civil rights activist from which country?',
            answer: 'India'
        },
        {
            question: 'During the American Revolution, the British army was popular nicknamed as?',
            answer: 'Red Coats'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the name of the Candian national anthem?',
            answer: 'O Canada'
        }
    ]
]